What do you want to see, baby?
For 200 coins,
I'll give you what you want.
What?
I said 200 for two.
That's what I'm saying, baby.
Oh, shit!
One moment guys...
Go on...
- I’ll go.
- You should rest.
Go ahead.
“Collab.”
“We thought it was a collab.”
“One thousand coins for a collab.”
Collab?
With whom?
With Cara?
“We want some F2F action.”
Oh, you guys...
Date?
Uh...
Yeah, it's been a while since
Migo and I saw each other.
How about you, do you have work?
Isn't it your day off?
Our client said there's
an emergency meeting.
Oh...
Okay, good luck.
Hey, girl...
- By the way...
- What?
My...
My share of the apartment rent...
can I pass for now?
The client hasn't paid yet.
Hmm...
Okay. I'll try to
borrow from Migo,
but make sure to pay because you know,
I don't have extra funds.
Of course, girl.
- Okay, then... bye.
- Take care.
- Bye!
- Enjoy!
Hi, Boss! Good morning!
Hi, Ella.
This meeting will be short.
The company reviewed its finances
and it looks like we need to let you go.
Sir?
Is it my rate?
I can lower my hourly rate.
I'm sorry, Ella.
We're just in a tight spot
and we can no longer afford
your services.
If you need recommendations,
I can give you one.
Babe, aren't we going to miss
the restaurant?
It’s getting late.
Shh... we'll find another place.
Migo, it's been so long
since we last saw each other.
You prioritized
that student council thing...
Shh... I'm almost there.
Thanks babe...
I’ll...
I'll freshen up,
then we can go, okay?
Hey! When are you
coming to my dorm?
I’m all alone.
- Babe, I can explain...
- Damn you, Migo!
How I wish...
Have some guts, Ella!
[sighs]
"Hey!"
“I saw your post.”
“You’re looking great.”
“Maybe you can let me in
on your business.”
Where are you?
Migo is looking for you.
He said you fought with him.
Ma, please don’t get involved
this time, okay?
What did you fight about?
Are you just being
a drama queen again?
Ma, he cheated on me,
he was with another woman.
He said he was just busy
with that damn student council.
And I, like a fool, believed him.
I thought maybe he was just busy
with his campaign.
And then what?
I find out he's just cheating on me?
Maybe Migo is just stressed.
His father has high expectations of him.
People make mistakes.
Don't you love him anymore?
Ma, are you siding with him?
I’m not that stupid!
It's your decision...
I'm just saying...
can you handle it?
Why wouldn't I handle it?
Who does he think he is?
No one will drive you
to school anymore.
No one will give you the gifts you want.
Remember, you got to tour Hong Kong
because Migo's family brought you along.
Think about it, dear.
Damn it!
Are you cursing at me, dear?
Hey...
What happened to you?
Migo and I broke up...
What?
Did you manage to borrow
the money I need?
- Ella, come on!
- Just kidding!
What happened?
The jerk is seeing another girl.
But I'm not sure
if I made the right decision.
Of course you did!
What are you thinking?
Don't let anyone cheat on you
and treat you like trash.
Do you want us to get back at him?
[whining]
Good thing the guard let you in.
I said I was getting my transcript.
So, what's up?
How are you?
That’s just it...
Do you have a side gig for me?
Aren't you working as a virtual assistant?
You were making good money there, right?
I got let go.
I really need work now.
So many bills...
Plus, tuition fees are due.
What if I just lend you the money?
Because you might not be able
to handle the work.
I need a job more.
I can handle it. Anything.
Well... Are you familiar
with PleasureHub?
You make porn?
Well, let's just say...
I'm a PleasureHub model.
I do shows on the webcam.
Whatever the audience wants, I do it.
You have a nice body.
You're beautiful...
Why don’t you use it?
What if someone recognizes me?
So what?
Do they feed you?
Do they pay your bills?
Just follow my lead.
Right now, I have 25 thousand subscribers.
We can collaborate on one, or two videos,
so you can get some of my subs.
Then you can create your own account.
What would I do on my own account?
Touch yourself...
Masturbate...
Read the comments from time to time,
because sometimes
they just want to see you eat...
while naked.
- And they’ll pay for that?
- Of course! Plus tips.
This is so difficult!
Nobody's giving coins!
Just be patient.
Excuse me...
Is this the list of scholars?
- What are you doing here?
- Cara, please, talk to me.
Cara, I know I was wrong...
I’m just human, I make mistakes.
I get tempted.
But I never doubted my feelings.
- You’re the one I love.
- I told you to stop it!
I don’t have time for your nonsense!
Cara, please...
Sir, is the list of scholars
posted on the bulletin final?
Yes, hija.
My name isn't on the list.
But I'm a scholar.
What's your full name?
Cara Sta. Ines...
It looks like you dropped
out of the ranking this semester.
There are too many applicants
for the scholarship,
so the committee raised the cut-off.
- Can I still petition?
- Yes, you can...
but hearings for those petitions
take a long time.
I suggest that you apply again
next semester.
- Okay?
- Okay, sir.
Migo told me your scholarship got revoked.
He’s willing to lend you money.
I don’t have any money to lend you.
Don’t tell me Migo
is bothering you again?
What happened?
- I lost my scholarship.
- What?
How did that happen when your grades
are so high?
They raised the cut-off...
and my mom
is also adding to the pressure.
She wants me to make up with Migo,
because he’ll be willing
to lend me tuition money.
But damn it!
It would feel like eating shit!
He already cheated on me,
and now I’m supposed to tolerate it?
If there’s really no other option,
then go ahead...
But let’s try to find
another way first, okay?
What about you?
How did you find money for your tuition?
I have a new side gig...
Can I join?
Let’s see. I’ll let you know.
Thank you!
Did you cook?
Crazy, of course not!
- I ordered food.
- Wow, you have a budget.
I also paid the water, electricity bills,
and the rent.
Let’s eat.
I haven’t forgotten
our conversation last night.
- What conversation?
- That you’d get me into your gig.
Oh...
Are you familiar with PleasureHub?
What’s that?
That’s my gig...
Ella... why are you doing this?
Why not? I’m able to pay my bills
and tuition, right?
Do people really pay for this?
Well...
honestly,
after several days,
I only get a few dollars.
I’d be lucky if I make 50 dollars
in one live...
Then last night,
when you walked into my room,
my live caught you on camera.
And my audience showered me with tips
when they saw you.
What does that mean?
They got excited seeing us.
The both of us...
together in one video.
They want us to collab...
- that’s if you’re interested.
- Collab?
We do a show together live.
Are you crazy?
Why would I do that?
You said you need
money for tuition, right?
Do you prefer to borrow
from that cheater, Migo?
Sorry, but I don’t know
if I can do that.
Okay, fine. No problem.
Wait.
That’s yours.
That’s the tip I got
just because you appeared in my live.
- Are you bribing me?
- Of course not!
I just want you to imagine
how much more you could earn
if we go live together.
Come on, guys,
let us know what you want us to do.
Do you want to see us kiss?
Or...
touch each other’s boobs?
Pass the candy?
Do you want...
Uh... Do you want me
to pass my candy to her?
Show me some coins...
Oh! Look!
Okay... Thank you! Thank you!
Okay, I’ll pass my candy now...
What’s next?
Again?
Again... Again...
Okay. Okay...
Oh! Thank you!
Okay, I’ll...
I’ll feed her now...
So? Is this enough
until next semester?
If we don’t eat or pay our bills.
What else do you want me to do?
I’m even willing to be corny for you.
I don’t do that for any other girl.
Wow, did I force you to do that?
Should I thank you?
I already told you,
leave me alone.
Move.
I miss you so much.
Please come back...
Ella and I have something to do.
I need to go home.
[sighs] You know...
I feel like you’re acting this way
because of Ella.
Stay away from her!
I know you live together
at the apartment,
but she’s a bad influence.
What do you mean?
Someone saw her the other day...
she was talking to Melody.
She got kicked out remember?
For being a professor's sugar baby.
Maybe Ella’s the same.
You’re a good girl...
that’s why I love you.
Ella’s not like that.
My friend isn’t like that.
And if anyone’s the jerk
between the two of you, it’s you!
Please, don’t bring that up again.
I made a mistake,
and I’m sorry.
I just needed to release some tension
because I was so stressed out.
But you’re the one I love.
I can’t lose you...
Hey, guys!
So, we have a glow-in-the-dark dildo.
You can see it in action for 300 coins...
Cara will be here soon, don’t worry.
Hey...
Why are you in such a rush?
There’s no classes, it’s a weekend.
Exactly. I'm meeting up with Migo.
Cara, are you sure
about what you're doing?
Dear, don’t worry...
I’ll still help with PleasureHub.
Besides, I also need to earn some money...
Then why go back to Migo?
You don’t need him anymore.
I felt that his apology was genuine.
You know, we should hang out sometime,
the three of us.
So you can see that he's really okay.
Oh!
Wait.
- Hello, babe?
- Babe, I'll pick you up in 30 minutes?
Okay, sure, I’ll get ready.
Okay, bye.
I need to go...
- Cheers!
- Cheers everyone!
That’s solid!
[groans]
- One more!
- One more?
Not too much...
Dear, just a reminder,
your tolerance for alcohol is low.
Migo is here...
Come on.
I can take care of my girl.
More shots!
- Shot!
- Let’s go!
Shot!
Cheers!
Yeah, Ella...
Don’t be such a killjoy!
Ugh!
- Damn, it burns.
- Huh?
- It burns, baby?
- Mm-hmm.
Wait, wait...
- Does it still hurt?
- Yeah, it does!
Where? Here?
Oh!
One more...
- I think it still hurts...
- Yeah, here...
What is it?
Lie down...
Migo, I think Cara and I should go home.
We’ll just call a taxi.
Why?
She’s tired and drunk.
If you want, you can
sleep on the sofa.
Yeah, yeah...
- We need to go home, babe...
- Babe, just rest here.
Hmm...
I’ll just get some water
to help sober her up.
Okay... Take care!
Babe...
Help me up...
- Wait.
- Shh...
- I want to go home...
- Shut up, babe.
- Babe...
- Just sleep here with me.
You know...
I have a film project with...
Ella.
- Project?
- Yeah, film project.
Wait, wait...
here it is.
Look.
[giggling]
What the hell?
What’s this?
- You like it?
- Are you messing with me?
So you’re the only one
who gets to have sex with others?
[chuckles]
- The hell...
- Woah, woah!
Wait...
Isn’t this every guy’s fantasy?
Girl on girl action!
You’re disgusting!
What did you do to my girlfriend?
This has to be your influence!
- What’s going on?
- That!
Cara... what did you do?
I just showed Migo our project.
You know what?
Just get out!
Both of you, leave!
[groans] I heard you... Wait.
Screw you!
Do you remember anything
from last night?
Last night?
Mmm...
I remember you dancing with Paul,
while you were making out.
And he was grinding
his dick against you.
Cara, that’s not what I meant.
You don’t remember
what you did to Migo?
You showed him the PleasureHub.
I know.
He’s been texting me all sorts of crap.
Says I’m trash.
So, what’s your plan?
Plan?
Well...
If he can’t accept what I do,
he doesn’t deserve me.
What’s important is...
are you still in?
Of course.
And I don't care if I lose Migo,
as long as it's not you.
Why would you lose me?
I’m not going anywhere.
What are you doing?
Don’t you feel what I feel?
What are we, Ella?
What are you talking about?
Of course you’re my friend.
Come on, Ella.
This is all new to you...
Maybe you’re just confused.
Stop harassing Ella!
Stop it with me too!
Why?
Your friend is really a slut, right?
She even got you involved.
Your dick is so small, asshole!
[people laughing]
What are you laughing at?
Can we talk?
I'm so sorry. It's fine
if you don't like me back.
But please, let's be friends.
Okay!
You nosy assholes!
You really want to know
why Cara isn't here?
English your face!
Cara confessed to me.
She said...
she likes me.
What am I supposed to say to that?
Do I not want to lose her?
I don't!
Do I not want to hurt her?
Of course...
Am I jealous when
she's with her ex?
I think so...
I don't know.
Whatever...
All I know is,
she's important to me.
Is that love?
Maybe...
I'm sorry.
I heard everything.
I heard it all...
We'll figure this out, okay?
We'll figure this out.